(this.webpackJsonpyopardy=this.webpackJsonpyopardy||[]).push([[0],{12:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"name":"JS","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"When this is used, a variable can not be reassigned.","answer":"const"},{"value":200,"question":"The context in which values are visible or can be referenced.","answer":"scope"},{"value":300,"question":"The combination of a function with reference to its lexical environment.","answer":"Closure"},{"value":400,"question":"The three most common ways to handle asynchronous operations in JavaScript.","answer":"Callbacks, Promises, async/await"},{"value":500,"question":"This is JavaScript\'s inheritance model.","answer":"Prototypal inheritance"}]},{"name":"CS","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"The repetition of a sequence of computer instructions a specified number of times or until a condition is met.","answer":"loop"},{"value":200,"question":"Time required for a function to execute based on its input size.","answer":"Time complexity"},{"value":300,"question":"A function or algorithm that calls itself one or more times until a specified condition is met.","answer":"Recursion"},{"value":400,"question":"A form of automatic memory management which reclaims memory occupied by objects that are no longer in use by the program.","answer":"Garbage collection"},{"value":500,"question":"In this data structure, for any given node C, if P is a parent node of C, then the key (the value) of P is greater than or equal to the key of C.","answer":"Heap"}]},{"name":"BACKEND","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"Computer program or a device that provides functionality for other programs or devices, called \\"clients\\".","answer":"Server"},{"value":200,"question":"A popular Node framework, used to write handlers for requests with different HTTP verbs at different URL paths.","answer":"Express"},{"value":300,"question":"A small piece of data sent from a website and stored on the user\'s computer by the user\'s web browser while the user is browsing.","answer":"Cookie"},{"value":400,"question":"Refers to the management of incremental, reversible changes and version control for relational database schemas.","answer":"Schema migration"},{"value":500,"question":"A device that acts as a reverse proxy and distributes network or application traffic across a number of servers.","answer":"Load Balancer"}]},{"name":"FRONTEND","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"The API to a webpage, allowing programs to read and manipulate the page content, structure, and styles.","answer":"DOM"},{"value":200,"question":"Describes all HTML elements, and includes content, padding, border and margin.","answer":"The CSS box model"},{"value":300,"question":"Elements that clearly describe their meaning to both the browser and the developer, as well as providing enhanced accessibility.","answer":"Semantic elements"},{"value":400,"question":"A React hook which serves the same purpose as componentDidMount, componentDidUpdate, and componentWillUnmount did in class\u2014based React, but unified into a single API.","answer":"useEffect"},{"value":500,"question":"A JavaScript API for rendering interactive 2D and 3D graphics within any compatible web browser.","answer":"WebGL"}]},{"name":"CI/CD","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"A software development practice where members of a team combine their work frequently.","answer":"Continuous Integration"},{"value":200,"question":"It advocates adaptive planning, evolutionary development, early delivery, and continual improvement, and it encourages rapid and flexible response to change.","answer":"Agile"},{"value":300,"question":"Used to help a product manager (and others in the organization involved with the product\'s development) understand key traits, behaviors, goals, responsibilities, and needs of a specific type of user.","answer":"Persona"},{"value":400,"question":"The process of taking code from version control and making it readily available to users of your application in an automated fashion.","answer":"Deployment pipeline"},{"value":500,"question":"Factor (from XII Factors) in which a developer resists the urge to use different backing services between development and production","answer":"Dev/Prod Parity"}]}]')},15:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(34)},20:function(e,t,a){},34:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),r=a.n(n),s=a(10),o=a.n(s),i=(a(20),function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"header"},"\ud83c\udf4d y o p a r d y")}),c=a(4),l=a(11),u=Object(l.a)((function(e,t){return{team:"t1",setTeam:function(t){return e({team:t})},selected:"",setSelected:function(t){e({selected:t})},answered:[],setAnswered:function(t){localStorage.setItem("answered",JSON.stringify(t)),e({answered:t})},score:{t1:0,t2:0,t3:0},setScore:function(t){localStorage.setItem("score",JSON.stringify(t));var a={score:t,lastUpdated:(new Date).toString()};e({scoreLastUpdated:a}),e({score:t})},scoreLastUpdated:{score:{t1:0,t2:0,t3:0},lastUpdated:(new Date).toString()},setScoreLastUpdated:function(t){return e({scoreLastUpdated:t})},reset:function(){var t={t1:0,t2:0,t3:0},a=[];localStorage.setItem("score",JSON.stringify(t)),localStorage.setItem("answered",JSON.stringify(a)),e({answered:a}),e({score:t})}}})),m=Object(c.a)(u,1)[0],d=Object(n.memo)((function(e){var t=e.value,a=e.question,s=m((function(e){return e.setSelected})),o=m((function(e){return e.answered})),i=Object(n.useCallback)((function(){s(a)}),[s,a]);return r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement("div",{onClick:i,className:"question"},o.includes(a.question)?"\ud83e\udd51":t))})),f=a(3),p=a.n(f),v=function(e){var t=e.name,a=e.questions;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"column"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"column-header"},t),a.map((function(e){return r.a.createElement(d,{qid:e.id,key:p.a.generate(),value:e.value,question:e,answers:e.answers})})))},b=a(12),h=function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"questions"},b.map((function(e){return r.a.createElement(v,{key:p.a.generate(),name:e.name,questions:e.questions})})))},w=Object(n.memo)((function(){var e=m((function(e){return e.setTeam})),t=m((function(e){return e.team})),a=m((function(e){return e.score})),s=Object(n.useCallback)((function(t){e(t)}),[e]);return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"teams"},r.a.createElement("div",{onClick:function(e){s(e.target.id)},className:"team ".concat("t1"===t&&"team-selected"),id:"t1"},"TEAM 1 ","t1"===t?"\ud83d\udd2e":"\ud83d\udc85\ud83c\udffc",r.a.createElement("div",{className:"".concat(a.t1<0?"score-negative":"score-display")},a.t1)),r.a.createElement("div",{onClick:function(e){s(e.target.id)},className:"team ".concat("t2"===t&&"team-selected"),id:"t2"},"TEAM 2 ","t2"===t?"\ud83d\udd2e":"\ud83d\udc85\ud83c\udffc",r.a.createElement("div",{className:"".concat(a.t2<0?"score-negative":"score-display")},a.t2)),r.a.createElement("div",{onClick:function(e){s(e.target.id)},className:"team ".concat("t3"===t&&"team-selected"),id:"t3"},"TEAM 3 ","t3"===t?"\ud83d\udd2e":"\ud83d\udc85\ud83c\udffc",r.a.createElement("div",{className:"".concat(a.t3<0?"score-negative":"score-display")},a.t3)))})),g=a(14),E=a(1),q=a(5),y=a(6),S=a.n(y),N=function(e){var t=m((function(e){return e.selected})),a=m((function(e){return e.setSelected})),s=m((function(e){return e.score})),o=m((function(e){return e.setScore})),i=m((function(e){return e.team})),l=Object(n.useState)(!1),u=Object(c.a)(l,2),d=u[0],f=u[1],p=m((function(e){return e.answered})),v=m((function(e){return e.setAnswered})),b=function(e){o(!0===e?Object(q.a)({},s,Object(E.a)({},i,s[i]+t.value)):Object(q.a)({},s,Object(E.a)({},i,s[i]-t.value/2>0?s[i]-t.value/2:0))),a(null),f(!d)};return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-modal"},r.a.createElement(S.a,{bottom:!0},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-modal-question"},t.question)),d?r.a.createElement(S.a,{bottom:!0},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-modal-answer"},t.answer.toUpperCase())):r.a.createElement("button",{className:"show-answer-button",onClick:function(){f(!d),v([].concat(Object(g.a)(p),[t.question]))}},"SHOW ANSWER"),d&&r.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-buttons"},r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return b(!0)},className:"hell-yeah-button"},"HELL YEAH!"," ",r.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":"red cross"},"\u2705")),r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return b(!1)},className:"close-modal-button"},d?"NOPE":"CLOSE"," ",r.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":"red cross"},"\u274c"))))},C=a(13),O=a.n(C);var k=function(){var e=m((function(e){return e.setScore})),t=m((function(e){return e.setAnswered})),a=m((function(e){return e.reset})),s=m((function(e){return e.selected})),o=m((function(e){return e.scoreLastUpdated})),c=Object(n.useCallback)((function(){var t=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("score"));t&&e(t)}),[e]),l=Object(n.useCallback)((function(){var e=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("answered"));e&&t(e)}),[t]);return Object(n.useEffect)((function(){c(),l()}),[c,l]),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement(i,null),r.a.createElement(h,null),r.a.createElement(w,null),s&&r.a.createElement(N,null),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-last-updated"},"SCORE LAST UPDATED:"," ",O()(o.lastUpdated).format("MMMM Do YYYY, h:mm:ss a").toUpperCase()),r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){a()},className:"reset-score-button"},"RESET GAME"))};o.a.render(r.a.createElement(k,null),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[15,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.9577a9d5.chunk.js.map